// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'How many countries in the world still have a monarchy?', 
      a: '40', 
      b: '27',
      c: '43',
      d: '39',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'In the Princess Bride, what animal do they fight in the forest?', 
      a: 'Skunk', 
      b: 'Cat',
      c: 'Weasel',
      d: 'Rat',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which Disney Princess was the first princess to appear in a feature-length film?', 
      a: 'Snow White', 
      b: 'Cinderella',
      c: 'Persephone',
      d: 'Pochahontas',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which Princess a solar power company that provides street lights, reading lamps, and electricity to 620 million people in Africa?', 
      a: 'Keisha Omilana of Nigeria', 
      b: 'Abze Djigma of Burkina Faso',
      c: 'Sikhanyiso of Swaziland',
      d: 'Sylvia Nagginda of Buganda',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'The inspiration for Ariel from Little Mermaid’s look was based on which actress’ face?', 
      a: 'Shannon Doherty', 
      b: 'Marcia Cross',
      c: 'Alyssa Milano',
      d: 'Holly Marie Combs',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What city did Princess Diana die in? #RIP', 
      a: 'Montreal, Canada', 
      b: 'London, England',
      c: 'Rome, Italy',
      d: 'Paris, France',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'In the esteemed 2001 film, Princess Diaries, where is the country of Genovia located?', 
      a: 'Between France and  Spain', 
      b: 'Next to Switzerland',
      c: 'Next to Russia',
      d: 'Between France and Italy',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Before she became Queen of England, Elizabeth joined the army as a:', 
      a: 'Nurse', 
      b: 'Mechanic',
      c: 'Chief Commander',
      d: 'Radar Operator',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'The only princess ever to win an Oscar is:', 
      a: 'Audrey Hepburn', 
      b: 'Meghan Markle',
      c: 'Grace Kelly ',
      d: 'Tilda Swinton',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Jane nicknamed me Princess in response to whose relentless and unfounded criticism?', 
      a: 'D-Rap', 
      b: 'Jlowe',
      c: 'Joco',
      d: 'RA',
      answer: 'b'
    }
  ]
};